[SINGING]
It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
Good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
ALL:
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
Positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
ALL:
He's a family guy
[CHATTERING]
Aw, I can't wait to see
all my old classmates.
This is gonna be
so much fun, isn't it, Peter?
Oh, sure. It's a blast being in
a room full of people you don't know.
I'd rather stay home
and watch grass grow.
- Come on, you. Come on.
- Hey, Peter.
Hey, Joe. Damn it!
You're not uncomfortable, are you?
Look, I'm just not wild about the idea of
running into anybody you used to date.
- That's all.
- Oh, boy.
- Speaking of exes. Here comes one now.
- Oh, man. This is what I was afraid of.
If he tries anything,
I'm gonna kick him right in the ball...
- gina?
- Peter, this is Naomi.
Wait. You mean, you
two used to, you know...
bump Japanese cartoon monkey
logo mouths?
Well, let's just say Naomi and I
experimented quite a bit in college.
No way! My wife messed
around with another chick?
- Thank you, God!
- Don't mention it, Peter.
[CHORUS SINGING ON-SCREEN TEXT]
Have fun!
Naomi, I'm so glad you're here.
I haven't seen you in, what, 20 years?
Oh, it's great to see you too, Lois.
It really is.
You know, the fact is, I came here
hoping to run into you.
Really? Well, that's nice.
You see, I'd like to propose something
to you and your husband.
Oh, my God. I'm dreaming.
I'm dreaming right now.
Well, of course, Naomi.
What did you have in mind?
Well, this really isn't the place
to discuss it.
It's just something I was wondering
if you and your husband...
would participate in.
- I'm totally dreaming right now.
Well, as long as I'm dreaming,
I might as well pee my pants.
Well, Naomi, whatever it is,
I'm sure we'd be happy to help.
Oh, my God. I don't believe it.
I'm gonna have a three-way!
This even tops sex with a mermaid!
- Where is it?
- Keep looking.
- I can't find it anywhere.
There's nothing but a fish tail
down there.
- Keep looking.
- Oh, there we go.
- That's not it.
- It's gonna be.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: We now return to
Nature with a guy named Terry in it.
[ROARS]
NARRATOR: The cheetahs will feed
through the night.
While the strongest made the kill,
the oldest will eat first.
And there's Terry.
She's gonna be here any minute.
You got to get out.
Why do we have to leave, Dad?
Because Daddy's
gonna have a three-way...
with your mother and her friend.
Isn't that nice about Daddy's three-way?
I had a one-way one time.
That was amazing.
Sorry I farted in the middle.
All right, go on. Beat it, all of you!
Peter, you're not gonna be having
a three-way. Lois isn't even into women.
She just had one experience
in college with that girl, Naomi.
Naomi's the one who's coming.
[CRYING]
Let me stay! Let me stay!
- Peter, why are you so antsy?
- Because Naomi will be here shortly...
and I'm anxious to get started.
What do you mean?
We don't even know why she's coming.
"We don't even know
why she's coming."
You are so adorable.
- I'm gonna do you second.
- Huh?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hi, Naomi. Did you pick up those
tear-away panties like I texted you?
I didn't get a text from you.
All right.
I'm not sure why, but I'll bite.
- Hi, Naomi.
- Hello, Lois.
- I want you to meet my husband, Dale.
- Hi. Nice to meet you, Dale.
Dale? All right, I guess.
But I'm doing you last.
Joke's on him. I only got two in me.
- Lois, this is such a lovely home.
- Oh, thank you.
Peter and I did it ourselves
on a shoestring.
- Well, you could have fooled me.
- Oh, ha, ha.
Well, let me show you around.
This here is our living room.
PETER: All right, I got a few
porn scenarios for you to choose from.
Hey, everybody. Got a pizza delivery
for this sorority house.
Did somebody order sausage?
[HUMMING PORN MUSIC]
Peter! What the hell are you doing?
Knock it off.
Uh, we brought you some wine,
but it's best chilled before dinner.
Oh, that is so nice of you.
Yeah, let's put it on ice.
Oh, you'll have to excuse my kitchen.
I've been cooking all...
Girls, I've just finished grading
your midterms and it's not good news.
Looks like you're gonna
have to do some extra credit.
[HUMMING PORN MUSIC]
Peter, what the hell?
I am so sorry about this.
Look, dinner's just about ready.
Why don't I get you seated in the dining
room and then we'll pour the wine?
All right, new arrivals,
there's only one way...
you're not getting on that train.
[HUMMING PORN MUSIC]
We got a few hours to kill.
What do you want to do?
- Let's get something to eat.
- We don't have any money.
Pull over there.
I'll get us some money.
Now, wait. So the white ball
has to hit one of the stripy balls?
Yes. How many times
you gonna ask me that?
I don't know. I'm just a baby.
All right, so I guess I'II, um...
- What is it you call it?
- Break.
Break. Right, break.
Oh, my God! Beginner's luck, huh?
Start the car! Start the car! Go, go, go!
- We been hustled!
- Nobody says that anymore.
- What would you call it?
- I wouldn't comment on it.
We know what happened.
And so I went into corporate finance,
and that's where I met Dale.
Six months later,
I was asking her to marry me.
What took me so long, right?
[ALL LAUGHING]
All right. We're running out of time.
- We gonna get this orgy started or what?
- What?
[SLOWLY]
We are running out of time.
Are we going to get
this orgy started or what?
Oh, my God! You thought
that's what we were here for?
- You're not?
- No!
Well, then, what are you doing here?
Dale and I found out
that we can't have children.
We've conceived many times, but for
some reason the eggs won't attach.
It was suggested I find
a woman who would consider...
carrying our child to term.
And, well, Lois, that's why we're here.
We were wondering if you would
be our surrogate.
Oh, my God!
You want me to carry your child?
- Yes.
- What?
I don't know what this is about.
But you're my best friend, and I'd like
to think that you'd do the same for me.
Wait a minute.
So you guys can't have a baby?
Unfortunately, no.
Well, whose fault is it?
I mean, which one of you...
has the thing that's horribly wrong
with them? Is it you, Naomi?
- You got a bum cervix?
- Peter! It's nobody's fault.
- Conception is complicated.
- Dale, it's you. You got a bum dong.
Will you help us, Lois?
Well, l... I'm honored
that you would ask me, Naomi.
L... I'll have to think about it.
I mean, this is a life-altering choice.
You know, like an Italian
choosing to get glasses.
Okay, read the third row down, please.
"A-A-O-A-O-O-A."
Everyone, I have something to say.
I've given this
long and careful thought.
And I've decided to carry
Naomi and Dale's child for them.
- You what?
- That's right.
I want your blessing, Peter.
You'll have my stool in your eye,
and that's all. You can't have their baby!
Yeah, Mom. You get crazy
when you're pregnant.
Mom, I can't find my jacket.
[LAUGHING]
[SOBBING]
[SCREAMS] Peter, take off that belt!
The buckle smells like acid!
[SOBS]
[COUGHING]
[MOANING]
Look, I know it's an inconvenience,
but it's a wonderful gift...
to be able to give someone.
So I am going through with it.
Well, I support you, Lois.
I think it's great what you're doing.
Yeah, great. You're treating
your vagina like a Red Roof Inn.
She's doing something wonderful...
for a couple who can't have children
and are too egotistical to adopt.
You know what's interesting
about Lois's vagina?
Everyone in this room has
been in there except for you.
You're the only one
who doesn't know what it's like.
Lois, I don't want you
pregnant for nine months...
just to hand over the thing
when it comes out.
I mean, why does it got to be you?
Because they need a healthy female
body to carry the baby.
I can do it.
It was hard enough on your body
when you gave birth to Stewie.
- What?
- Ha-ha-ha.
I'm just joking!
Oh, not cool.
But really, Meg, you don't know
anything about this stuff.
You've never even had a boyfriend
more than a few weeks.
I have too.
Remember when I dated the Count?
One nipple. Ha-ha-ha!
Two nipples. Ha-ha-ha!
Three nip...
Oh, hell, no. I'm out of here.
All right, then. It's settled.
I'm gonna do this.
No, you're not, Lois.
I'm sorry, but I forbid it!
Oh, and I'm supposed to go along...
with everything you decide
for both of us?
Yes, Lois. That's how we coexist.
Just like I coexist with the tiny race
of people who live in our carpet.
[FAINT MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, what's that? I think I hear music.
Oh, that's the little people, Chris.
They're playing music so that I will
bless them with food.
[CHEERING]
Lois, Dale and I
just want to thank you again.
You're making us so happy.
Well, I wish my husband
felt the same way you do.
But he's just gonna have to accept it.
Mrs. Griffin, you should
understand a procedure like this...
is not without its risks. Here's what
happened when we fertilized an egg...
from Shelley Duvall
with a sperm from James Blunt.
Here's Hilary Swank and Gary Busey.
Florence Griffith-Joyner
and Stephen Hawking.
- Okay. I think that's enough.
- I got more funny ones.
I got Tina Fey and Joaquin Phoenix.
- Yeah, I think we're fine.
- Lot of face stuff going on.
- Let's just get to it.
- The eggs have been fertilized...
by means of intracytoplasmic
sperm injection.
And now the embryos
will be inserted.
The insertion procedure
will be performed...
by these South American Hovitos
blow-gunners.
Wait a minute. I don't want them
shooting things into my vagina.
Well, perhaps you could tell them,
if only you spoke Hovitos.
[BLOW GUNS SHOOTING]
[LOIS SCREAMING]
I can't believe
she went ahead and did it...
after I specifically told her
how I felt.
Clearly she believed it was
within her right to...
Lois just peed on something.
- Hey, Brian, you picking up on that?
- Yup.
LOIS:
It worked, everybody! I'm pregnant!
Damn it! This has gone too far!
And if I'm gonna do something about it,
it's got to be now.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm not gonna do anything, Brian.
But sometimes things happen.
The house is a dangerous place...
for today's modern woman.
Rickety staircases, faulty wiring...
gay poltergeists.
Boo, to that outfit.
Lois, I've hired some 1980s
black break dancers...
to do their routine on your stomach.
Peter, come on! I'm having this baby
and that's the end of it.
But if they do it good enough,
they'll save the rec center...
from being torn down and replaced by
some mall. Ozone, Turbo, do your thing!
Oh, no. Lois, those are '90s black guys.
Those aren't '80s black guys at all! Run!
We're here to dance for the kids.
Run, '80s black guys!
You're no match for the '90s black guys!
[GASPING]
Oh.
[SIGHS]
Ow.
Lois, I bet I can drink
more bleach than you.
Okay, you know what, Peter? Stop it!
I know you're not happy about this...
but I am pregnant
and I am having this baby.
So knock it off because I have had it!
No, I've had it! I don't want you
pregnant! You'll be fat and cranky.
Your boobs will get big.
You'll stop your period.
Wait. How do I feel about this?
No. No, I'm against it, I say.
Peter, this is important. Naomi and Dale
are placing their trust in us.
And besides, it's just nine months,
then everything will be back to normal.
TUCKER [ON TV]: We interrupt
this program for breaking news.
A devastating pileup on l-95 has injured
eight people and killed two others.
Naomi and Dale Robinson
were pronounced dead on arrival...
at Quahog Hospital.
- Oh, my God!
In other news, a local man
has won the lottery.
Lucky Quahog resident Dale Robinson
has hit the jackpo... Oh, boy.
I still just...
I can't believe they're gone.
They had their whole lives
ahead of them.
I'll be the one to say it.
What are you gonna do about the baby?
Let's keep it for parts!
You know, Lois,
you're not a young woman.
That baby's gonna be
chromosomally damaged...
like those cats you see
in the Special Anima-lympics.
So, Whiskers, how does it feel
to finally win your event...
after years of training?
[MEOWING SLOWLY]
Why don't you put the baby
up for adoption?
Well, what do we do until then? We can't
afford nine months of medical bills.
Well, you could have an abortion.
Well, there you go, Lois. We abort it.
Send it on up to Dale and Naomi.
If they left their mittens here
you wouldn't keep them.
- Send them back. Abort the thing.
- Oh, I don't know, Peter.
No harm visiting
the Family Planning Center...
just to see what your options are.
- Oh, it's such a big decision.
Of course it's a big decision.
Life is full of big decisions.
Like deciding whether or not
to have Indian food.
Lois, do I need to do anything
tomorrow that doesn't involve...
me being bent over in excruciating
pain 3 feet from a toilet?
LOIS: No.
- Time for some tikka masala.
Doctor, I won't lie to you.
I'm a little uncertain about this.
That's perfectly natural, Mrs. Griffin.
And you should ask as many questions
as you can before you decide.
So how does it work, doc? You go
hacking at her like Sweeney Todd?
No, no. Good Lord! This is not 2005.
We've come a long way since then.
So you go stabbing in there
with a laser...
and you try to zap it out like burning
an ant with a magnifying glass?
- No, Mr. Griffin.
- What? So, what?
You hold her legs open
and send a pit bull in there?
You know, one of them
little rat hunting dogs?
And he comes back out with it
in his mouth and he goes:
[GROWLING]
And you can't get it away from him
because, you know, it's his thing.
No. Mr. Griffin, it's a very simple, safe
procedure in which we very precisely...
and delicately remove the embryo.
We do it all the time.
And I promise, it's virtually risk free.
Well, I have to say
I feel a little better about it.
I think this may be
the right thing to do.
Mrs. Griffin,
we have a saying around here:
- Let's keep abortion safe, legal, and rare.
- Okay. Well, why don't you get started?
I'm gonna go sit in the car and pretend
like I'm driving. I'm gonna be in a race.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, what are you guys
bellyaching about?
Sir, we are doing all that we can
to stop the killing...
of millions of unborn babies.
If you have a few moments...
I'd like you to watch
this video presentation.
Yeah, I got a few minutes.
My wife's getting an abortion.
Hello, friend. I hear you're
contemplating having an abortion.
But before you do, remember,
science has proven...
that within hours of conception,
a fetus has started a college fund...
and has already made your first
Mother's Day card out of macaroni.
Aw!
But don't take my word for it.
Just ask my little friend Ziggy.
Hi! I'm Ziggy the Zygote.
I'm looking forward to being
an active member of your community.
Can I hug you?
Ha-ha-ha. Of course you can, Ziggy.
Because even though they're not
visible yet, you already have tiny arms.
Arms that will one day work,
play, and fold in prayer.
- Yay!
- But uh-oh, what's this?
[SCREAMS]
Oh, my God!
Well, he's gone, just like so many
other promising human lives...
who were probably snuffed out
by abortion.
Like the guy
who would have killed Hitler.
Nice going, Schweinhund!
The fourth Stooge. That's right.
There were supposed
to be four Stooges.
It was gonna be hilarious!
And Osama bin Laden's
America-Ioving older brother.
I would have talked him out of it!
Wow, thanks a lot for 9/11,
abortion enthusiasts.
And remember,
not only is abortion murder...
but it's also larceny, jaywalking,
and securities fraud.
Did you know the baby you abort...
may also have a baby inside of it
that you're aborting?
Now that you know this,
do you want an abortion?
No! No, I do not!
Peter, what the hell are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Don't you worry, unborn fetus child.
I am here to save you and protect you.
I have seen the light!
Bless you, sir.
You should be very proud of yourself.
Oh, I am. Prouder than
when I was a peacock.
Griffin, nice work
on the Anderson account.
So how did it go at the clinic?
Fine at first,
but then there was a complication.
- We have decided against the procedure.
- Really? Why?
Because it's killing babies, Brian.
If God wanted us to kill babies,
he'd make them all Chinese girls.
Peter, it's not a baby.
It's a fertilized egg.
- It's the size of a pin tip.
- It's alive, isn't it?
To kill any living thing is an abortion.
The man outside the clinic told me.
And he had a t-shirt on that confirmed it.
Okay. Well, sperm is alive.
And every time you masturbate,
millions of them die.
So is it wrong to kill sperm?
Yes. Yes, it is.
No more masturbating in this house.
- What?
- Why?
Because masturbation is abortion.
But abortion helps me
get my homework done...
and sometimes I abort in my sleep.
What am I supposed to do about that?
Peter, I'm sorry
if you disagree with me.
But according to the law,
it is still my right to choose...
what I do with my body.
- Well, the law is wrong, Lois!
Okay, Peter, if you're so pro-life,
let me ask you this.
Would you go down to the orphanage
and claim an unwanted baby...
and take care of it?
- I'm here to save the unborn.
Once out of the vagina,
they can go fuck themselves.
What's inside Lois won't be
remotely human for six months.
There's no brain activity
until at least the 27th week.
It's still a person. It's a woman's
responsibility to carry it to term.
Well, what if a woman is raped?
Should've thought
before she asked me for directions.
- Huh?
- What about incest, Peter?
- What's incest?
- You know how Cousin Lou...
has that kid whose eyes touch?
You're saying Touch Eyes
doesn't deserve to exist?
You don't mind him
when you want a needle threaded.
- They should have had the option.
- How can you say that?
Think of all the love he's given
to Uncle Mom and Aunt Dad?
Okay, this isn't working.
What if carrying the baby to term...
would endanger the mother's life?
I don't know seven of those words.
What if you see that the baby's gonna
be born with no arms and no legs?
You name it Mat.
[HONKING]
Peter, I honestly don't care
what you say.
I am going back to that clinic
and I'm having that abortion.
- Oh, no, you're not!
- Oh, yes, I am!
Now, you get out of my way.
You go and I'll blow the place up!
- You wouldn't.
- You've seen Family Guy. I would.
So, what,
you'd kill a bunch of doctors...
to show them that killing is wrong?
Does that make sense to you, Peter?
- Well...
- Does it?
I...
guess not.
- So, what the hell do we do, huh?
I mean,
we're not gonna solve anything...
by standing here
screaming at each other.
You and I are in this together, Peter.
And whatever we decide, we both have
to agree that it's the right thing to do.
Well, so now what?
I say we go upstairs
and have a long talk.
And we don't come down
until we've made a decision...
that we both can live with.
[SIGHS]
All right, Lois.
Well, I think we made
the right decision.
I mean, sure, having a baby
costs a fortune.
There's cutbacks on things we love.
There's diapers, and crying,
and late nights with no sleep.
Flu shots, and mumps,
and driver's ed, and college tuition.
But you know what?
It's one more person
to share the world with.
Another little voice
in the back seat of the car.
One more Griffin to love
and to love us in return.
We had the abortion.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru